All pirates searching for the treasure of One Piece must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Gold Roger and his crew were the only men to ever chart these waters and learn all the secrets they held.
For the rest of the pirates of the world, this has proven to be the end of the road, a graveyard of dreams.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber after eating the gum gum fruit, set sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I'm gonna be the king of the pirates!
Two years have passed since the War of the Best in Marineford. Luffy and his crew reunite to continue on to the New World.
The first stop on their journey is Fishman Island, which resides thousands of feet below ceiling.
Now, they're separated once again, stirring up trouble all over the ocean floor.
And now, we will restore his dream.
The new Fishman Pirates continue his legacy!
What?
Shark Crib.
Okay, I am so not into this! I'll check you later!
Kami, I need a favor from you.
Come on, Zoro! Let's move!
Listen up! Do me a favor and help those two get out of here!
And what about you?
We're not gonna make it out of here! Not if that guy's chasing us!
This is a revolution!
And you're in the way.
I, uh...
Well, um...
You see...
Good job! You found me!
She's huge!
Oh no!
Is she...
A cheese...
The pirates! They kidnapped the princess!
No, it's nothing! No matter what you hear, please don't turn around!
Huh? Why? What's the big deal?
Don't do it! I don't want you to die, Tadji!
Keep Shirohoshi safe! Deccan close behind!
I'm coming, my love! Wherever you are, I'll find you!
It's either death or marriage for you!
No!
Waah! Ho, ho ho ho hooo!
Waah! Ho, ho ho ho, hooo!
That's...
Princes Shirohoshi.
They...
They really did it!
I did it! They kidnapped the princess!
Hey, what the hell? Why'd you get out of the shark, you big baby?
I'm ever so sorry, Luffy! Please don't get mad at me! I promise it wasn't my fault!
That monster made her cry! He's pure evil!
Oh, how could he? Or Princess Shirohoshi?
Wait...
Did he just...say...Princess?
Please don't! No, Sanji! Find the urge to look!
Hey, I need to know, if I turn around to look behind me...
Am I gonna see the mermaid, Princess?
I won't lie! She's behind you! And that's exactly why you can't turn around!
The sight of an average mermaid almost killed you!
If you see the mermaid, Princess...
Every last drop of blood in your body will spray out your nose like a geyser!
It feels like a geyser! And then you'll be dead!
The mermaid princess...
They say even Boa Hancock, the most beautiful woman in the world, pales in comparison.
She's the most gorgeous mermaid who ever lived. And now, she's right behind me!
No, Sanji! I'm begging you, don't turn around!
If you don't turn around!
Chopper...
It's true...
I could give up on my dreams and die a coward at a ripe old age...
But I'd rather reach for the stars...
And die right now!
What?! But you always told me your dream was to find the all-blue!
No!
Sanji!
That's her...
I never realized...
How meager my imagination is...
She's magnificent...
She is...
Quite simply...
Too beautiful...
For the mind...
To comprehend...
He turned to stone!
Princess Shirahoshi!
We've gotta rescue her somehow!
Are you crazy? These are the same pirates that overpowered the entire royal family!
I expected death by arterial nasal spray, but this is new! How do I even treat this?
Wait a sec... I wonder if his blood donors have something to do with this?
Oh! Wolfie! What did I do?
Hey! What happened, huh? Talk to me, Hachi! Just tell me what creeps did this to you!
What the hell are you morons doing?!
We caught them!
We actually did it! We got the straw hats!
Of course! Guys like us hunt sea kings for a living, so what are a couple of wussy pirates gonna do?
Those punks are out of their league down here!
That's what you get for messing with sea hunters, you jerks!
And here I thought the army was our only hope! Huzzah!
You guys are fishermen! You realize we're not fish, don't you?
Hey, I remember this, lowlife!
That's right! You used to be one of Arlong's goons, huh?
You're safe now, Princess! We saved you!
I say we turn them over to the ammo knights so they can cut their heads off!
Wait, it's not what you think! Please! Luffy's not a bad guy!
Hey, what is that?! There's something flying at us! Look!
Huh? Really? You think we're dumb enough to fall for the oldest trick in the damn book?
Huh? Huh?
What the? There really is something up there!
Gah!
It looks like coral!
Yeah, but there's someone on it!
Oh no...
Not good! It's Vanderdecken!
I found you, Princess!
I suspect!
Come here, sweetie!
Oh no! Please not now!
I bet he was in cahoots with these pirates!
He's turned on his own people!
Run, Princess! We'll handle this!
Just get out of here!
It's time for an answer, Shirahoshi!
It's either yes or death!
Death!
If you truly wish to live...
Then you'll marry me!
Wait, are you serious?
You've been throwing weapons at the castle trying to kill her for ten whole years now!
And you actually think she's gonna marry you?!
You're really twisted, Vanderdecken!
You make me sick!
The Princess has been forced to live locked up inside a tower for a whole decade thanks to your sick sense of romance!
Now you propose? Monster!
Now! Let's hear it!
Although, I do suspect that it's a yes!
Bah-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho!
Bah-ho-ho-ho-ho!
Wah-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho!
Say it!
Say yes!
Bah-ho-ho-ho!
Bah-ho-ho-ho-ho!
You're just not my type!
What?
No!
What?!
That's your only reason?!
You tough! Then who is your type, huh? After you've led me on for ten whole years?
If you refuse to love me, I refuse to let you exist! Drop dead, my darling!
Run, Princess Jirahoshi, run!
Hurry! We'll fend them off with our lives!
Don't you move, you big baby! And don't cry!
Have you caused enough trouble? Stop telling her what to do, you jerks!
You're one of Van Der Decken's lackeys, aren't you? You probably want the princess to die!
Look, I can't protect you if you run away!
Okay, I'll stay!
No, Princess!
Leave her alone, you scumbag! You make me sick, pirate!
I'm real sorry about this, guys! It's nothing personal! But you're... in my way!
Second gear!
Foofy!
He did that, with his hands tied up?!
Ugh!
Quit sticking your butt into my business! This is between us! You're the one who kidnapped her from the tower, aren't you?!
Listen, you jerk! I'm gonna make sure you never throw anything at anyone ever again!
You better hope you can back that up, or I'm gonna throw you both into a shallow grave!
Let's see you try!
You let me go now!
All right, now gum gum!
Let's go!
Hammer!
I'm gonna make sure you never throw anything at anyone ever again!
You better hope you can back that up, or I'm gonna throw you both into a shallow grave!
Let's see you try!
You let me go now!
All right, now gum gum!
Let's go!
Hammer!
naszej
Sherry
Kawaii
Ken
K
Food
Wait, he just, he just beat Vandertekan!
It looks like he's still alive, but now we can catch him.
Shark, we're together!
Hey, Sansie!
You okay?
Well, he turned a stone a few minutes back, but he's all smiles now, and he's conscious.
Okay, that's good to hear.
No, no, princess!
I must have died and gone to heaven!
My dream came true!
My life is complete!
Once again, pretty sure your actual dream was to finally all blue!
Hey, hurry it up!
Sorry!
But please stop yelling! It makes it hard for me to concentrate when you do! My heart's racing!
I don't get it! These people don't like us for some reason! We gotta hurry and get out of here!
Thanks a lot! Good job! Let's go!
Okay!
What are you doing, princess? Why did you untie him?
That evil pirate did this! He scared her so much she's brainwashed now!
Sorry for all the trouble!
Sorry for all the trouble! I'll be back home in time for dinner, I promise!
Okay, shark! Get movin'!
Get back, you peasants!
Stop them now!
WANASUBI!
Oh, hey! I think I know that dude!
Catch the C-bonds who attack the Sunny! He works for Deckett!
Oh no, it's the Great Monk!
Oh, crap!
Swat them down like the insects they are!
You got it, boys!
Now, second gear!
It's Gung-Gung!
Jack!
Oh, no!
He's the Great Monk!
Hey, I think I know that dude!
Catch the C-bonds who attack the Sunny! He works for Deckett!
Oh, no! It's the Great Monk!
Oh, crap!
Swat them down like the insects they are!
You got it, boys!
Now, second gear!
It's Gung-Gung!
Jack!
Pistol!
My tooth!
He broke it!
Damn worthless giant!
Okay!
Let's get a move on!
To the sea for it!
Yeah!
Hey! Hey, boss!
That pirate girl and her mermaid friend
just escaped the Ryugu Palace!
Who gives a damn?
Once I get rid of this annoyance,
I'll only have to deal with a feeble old fool
and his helpless ma.
Shorkaroos!
Nami-Chin, should we have left the others behind like that?
If anyone else tried to come, we would have been caught.
Seemed like they were in trouble, though.
Those guys are fine.
Don't worry, they always make it out alive somehow.
Yeah...
I mean, I know they're tough and all.
But there's something scary about Hordy.
Ha-Chin said he's strong, but more than that,
he's cruel and ruthless.
They can handle it.
They've grown stronger by leaps and bounds these past few years.
That aside,
can you tell me what this former warlord, Jinbei, is like?
Huh?
Oh, well...
It's true he's a pirate, but he's well-trusted on the island, and they respect him enough that he can visit the palace, too.
Really? That's interesting.
Especially since he was a part of Arlong's crew.
And now this Hordy guy is presenting himself like the second coming of Arlong.
And Jinbei made a point to warn Luffy not to fight him.
And now I'm pretty sure I know why that is.
Huh? He was trying to keep him safe, right?
Just in case, let's keep our fingers crossed that Zoro and the others don't push Hordy too far.
No matter what, though, I want to meet this Jinbei guy.
He's waiting for Luffy at the sea forest now, right?
We're a part of this, whether we like it or not.
The whole kingdom could topple, but I don't know anything about the history behind Hordy and his pirate crew.
I bet Jinbei could help us decide how to handle this.
Wait, do you really think so?
Kami.
I need to get to the sea forest.
Right.
Listen up, soldiers.
Sir, we swear we'll take care of Hordy and the rest of his crew immediately.
No, you won't.
Huh?
I'm too weak to give you my full assistance, and I can't let you sacrifice your lives like that.
We shall surrender the palace for the time being, and meet up with Fukaboshi.
We will fight back when the time is right.
Huh?
You can't mean that, sir.
We can't let the palace fall to this evil scum.
Damn it, Zoro.
I know you're strong, but do you really think you can beat a fish man in the water?
I'm so weak.
Usopp, I know these old bones aren't the priority, but I fear I may soon drown.
How are you gonna drown when you don't have lungs?
Good point.
You're getting weaker.
I can feel it.
You can't hold out for long.
Puny human.
Soro's gonna pass out soon.
That must be Hordy's plan.
There's no time.
Fall off!
No!
That must be Hordy's plan!
Tis no time!
Fall off!
Whoa!
That swordsman's as good as death.
Yeah, well, the moron challenged a fish man in the water,
so there's really only one way that fight can end.
You're pretty resilient, aren't you?
Now, it's time to die.
Your hero's at an end.
Miserable, worthless, primate!
Zoro!
Captain, no!
One sword style, blind strike!
Zoro and companions try to escape Ryugu Palace.
However, the new fish man pirates, powered by energy steroids, drive him into a corner once more.
Meanwhile, Jinbei reunites with Luffy in the sea forest.
And while Shirahoshi visits her mother's grave, he reveals his shocking connection to the fish man, Arlong.
On the next One Piece, the Straw Hats defeated, Hordy gains control of the Ryugu Palace.
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
And while Shirahoshi visits her mother's grave, he reveals his shocking connection to the fish man, Arlong.
On the next One Piece, the Straw Hats defeated, Hordy gains control of the Ryugu Palace.
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!